<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE reference PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.2 Reference//EN" "reference.dtd" [
]>
<reference id="reference_760c9c20-af1c-40c1-8ad1-e98b82856be1"><title>API Glossary</title><prolog><author>Linda Castellani</author></prolog><refbody><section>This section provides additional information and definitions for some of the parameters.</section><section>
            <table id="table_0fde16b0-f6ec-4cba-a743-b5bee8415d1f" frame="topbot" rowsep="1" colsep="0"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colwidth="1.0*" colnum="1" colname="c1"/><colspec colwidth="3.50*" colnum="2" colname="c2"/><colspec colwidth=".05*" colnum="3" colname="c3"/><thead><row><entry>Parameter</entry><entry>Definition</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>assetUid</entry><entry>For Intelligent Environments, an asset is a physical object, such as equipment or a device, such as a sensor, which has the capability to collect or exchange data. It corresponds to a deviceType, mediaType, or eventType. An asset can be a device such as a NODE (parent asset) or a camera, that can capture certain media and events.<p><image id="image_2cf6c5a0-9847-4cb2-ba4c-591c7a7afea6" href="i_asset_examples_graphic.png"/></p></entry></row><row><entry>locationUid</entry><entry>A location is a monitored area, such as a parking zone, walkway, or a traffic lane for a city; site, location, room, or zone for an enterprise.<p><image id="image_dd63b508-59a3-49ae-a5dc-3588dcc4b67a" href="i_location_examples_graphic.png"/></p></entry></row><row><entry>locationType</entry><entry>
                                                                                                <dl><dlentry><dt><u>ENVIRONMENTS</u></dt><dd>Insert one of the following codes for a specific location type for <b>ENVIRONMENTS</b>: </dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>ENT_OFFICE_SPACE</dt><dd>ENT_OFFICE_SPACE consists of office spaces within boundaries. </dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>ENT_RETAIL_SPACE</dt><dd>ENT_RETAIL_SPACE consists of retails stores within boundaries. </dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt><u>CITIES</u></dt><dd>Insert on of the following codes for a specific location type for <b>CITIES</b>:</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>OTHERS</dt><dd>OTHERS consists of non-standard location types within the boundaries.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>PARKING SPOT</dt><dd>If you filter by PARKING_SPOT, you receive a list of demarcated parking spaces within the boundaries. (Not applicable in v2.)</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>PARKING_ZONE</dt><dd>PARKING_ZONE consists of four GEO coordinates of non-demarcated parking spaces within the boundaries.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>TRAFFIC_ZONE</dt><dd>TRAFFIC_ZONE consists of two GEO coordinates indicating a trip wire in traffic lanes within the boundaries.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>WALKWAY</dt><dd>WALKWAY consists of two GEO coordinates indicate a trip wire in pedestrian walkways within the boundaries.</dd></dlentry></dl>
                                                                                    </entry></row><row><entry>node</entry><entry>A node is a parent asset to other device types. A node can be an intelligent lighting apparatus, while an installed device type can be a camera, microphone, and/or environmental sensor. More than one device type can be installed on the node. See the Bounding Box graphic below.</entry></row><row><entry>bbox</entry><entry>A bounding box (bbox) establishes the periphery of a searchable area. You define a bounding box using GPS coordinates obtained from a map application such as Google Maps. For information on defining bounding boxes, see the query parameters in the "Simulated Data Stream Information for each API" table. A node can have any or all of the devices attached. The following assets reside within a bound area:<p><image id="image_7b23cb1d-7b06-425e-85b4-baded818f6c8" href="i_bbox_graphic.png"/></p></entry></row><row><entry>eventType</entry><entry>
                                                                                                <dl><dlentry><dt><u>CITIES</u></dt><dd>Insert one of the following codes for a specific event type for <b>CITIES</b>:</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>PKIN</dt><dd>If you filter by PKIN, you receive a list of vehicles (identified by objectUid) entering parking areas within the boundaries.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>PKOUT</dt><dd>If you filter by PKOUT you receive a list of vehicles (identified by objectUid) exiting parking areas within the boundaries.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>PEDEVT</dt><dd>If you filter by PEDEVT, you receive a list of pedestrian flow data</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>TFEVT</dt><dd>If you filter by TFEVT, you receive a list of traffic flow data.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt><u>ENTERPRISES</u></dt><dd>Insert on of the following codes for a specific event type for <b>ENTERPRISES</b>:</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>CO2</dt><dd>If you filter by CO2, you receive a list of assets that report sensor events for carbon dioxide level changes. </dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>ENCHG</dt><dd>If you filter by ENCHG, you receive a list of changed environmental conditions, such as temperature.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>HUMIDITY</dt><dd>If you filter by HUMIDITY, you receive a list of assets that report sensor events for humidity level changes.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>LIGHT_LEVEL</dt><dd>If you filter by LIGHT_LEVEL, you receive a list of assets that report sensor events for illuminance (ambient light level) changes.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>OCCUPANCY</dt><dd>If you filter by OCCUPANCY, you receive a list of assets that report sensor events for occupancy changes.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>TEMP</dt><dd>If you filter by TEMP, you receive a list of assets that report sensor events for temperature changes. </dd></dlentry></dl>
                                                                                    </entry></row><row><entry>timestamp</entry><entry>All timestamps are in UTC long format, representing the time in milliseconds in EPOCH format. To convert to EPOCH format, use the <xref scope="external" format="com" href="currentmillis.com">EPOCH converter</xref>. In addition, we have provided a moment.js which is available via the <xref scope="external" format="html" href="https://github.com/CurrentByGE/TrafficSeedApp/blob/master/app/elements/current-date-range-buttons/current-date-range-buttons.html">Traffic Seed App</xref>. If you use the same timestamp for start-ts and end-ts, a single result is returned.</entry></row><row><entry>mediaType<note>Get Media only works when you have access to Situational Awareness.</note></entry><entry>Insert one of the following enumeration codes for a specific media type.<dl><dlentry><dt>IMAGE</dt><dd>If you filter by IMAGE, you receive a list of images in JPG, PNG, or GIF formats.</dd><dd>Depending on the position of the camera, it will return the best resolution image available: either 320x240 for black and white or 1920x1080 for color.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>VIDEO</dt><dd>If you filter by VIDEO, you receive a list of videos in H.264 format.</dd><dd>By default, the video length is 1 minute. You can use VLC player to open the video.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>AUDIO</dt><dd>If you filter by AUDIO, you receive a list of audio files in MP3 or WAV format. This is not supported in v2.</dd></dlentry><dlentry><dt>OTHERS</dt><dd>If you filtered by OTHERS, you receive a list of non-standard formats.</dd></dlentry></dl></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>
        </section></refbody></reference>